A Finding Aid to the Jamison Thomas Gallery Records, 1940-2000, bulk 1980-1995, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Client and Collector Files, 1980-1995; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 4.5 Linear feet Boxes 3-7; 0.001 Gigabytes ER01
  - Individuals, 1980-1995; 2.2; Archival Resource Key
    - L.A. Clients Working File, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Leibman, Marvin, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Lewis, Sally Serkin, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Martin, Susan, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Miller, James, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Nakamura, Yoko, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Newburg, Gail, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Patton, Judy, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Rose, Judith, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Rosenak, Chuck and Jan, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Ross, Shelly, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco Clients, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Schnitzer, Arlene, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Semler, Herbert J., 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Skillern, Dana and Paul, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Skycraft, Peggy, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Spain, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Tonnemacher, David, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Valdivieso, Yvonne, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Various Consultants of General Interest, 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Corporate, 1985-1995; 2.3; Archival Resource Key
    The gallery's clients also included corporations who purchased or borrowed artworks for display in business spaces and exhibitions. Arranged here are correspondence, agreements, shipping notifications, and invoices. Notable corporate clients include Microsoft, Security Pacific Bank, and U.S. West Cellular.
    - Art Resources, Ltd., 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Avia, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Corporate Correspondence, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Crown Point Press, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Donnally Books, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Howard Hermanson Design, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Limited Editions Club, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Microsoft, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 40-41)
    - North Light Editions, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Oregon Trade and Marketing Center, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Parasol Press, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Security Pacific Bank, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - U.S. West Cellular, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Financial and Legal Records, 1980-2000; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 2.8 Linear feet Boxes 7-10
  Found here are stock inventory records, sales records including daily sales logs, and general operational financial and legal files.
  3.1: Inventory, 1986-1995
  3.2: Sales, 1985-1997
  3.3: Operations, 1980-2000
  - Inventory, 1986-1995; 3.1; Archival Resource Key
    Lists and correspondence about artworks at the gallery documenting the location of artworks, receipt of artworks, and potential sales or returns. Included here are inventory lists from the Jamison/Thomas Gallery of New York City, which opened in 1986 and was later named the Jeffrey Thomas Gallery. Along with some correspondence, these files document the transfer of artworks between the two gallery spaces.
    - Consignments, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Gallery Owned Inventory, 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 48-49)
    - Inventory Problems, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Jamison/Thomas Gallery NYC, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1-7)
    - Jeffrey Thomas Gallery, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
    - Miscellaneous Inventory Lists, 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Sales, 1985-1997; 3.2; Archival Resource Key
    Files include correspondence and records documenting the general sale of artworks to clients or galleries. Materials are comprised of daily sales logs, commissions and accounts payable reports, ledgers and receipt books.
    - Commissions, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
    - Daily Sales Logs, 1987-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13-18)
    - Ledgers, 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19-22)
    - Ledgers, 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
    - Ledgers, Gallery Closing, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Master Sold Lists, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Payments to Artists, 1985-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8-19)
    - Receipt Books, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Sales Records by Year, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Sales Reports, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Operations, 1980-2000; 3.3; Archival Resource Key
    Financial and legal materials pertaining to the everyday business operations of the gallery, including leases, contracts, banking materials, licenses, and tax forms.
    - 217 SW First Avenue, Portland, Oregon, circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - 300 SW First Avenue, Portland, Oregon, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - 1313 NW Glisan Street, Portland, Oregon, 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Accounts Payable, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Bank Loan Payments, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Business Licenses, 1984-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Consignment Contract Forms, 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Corporate Income Tax Returns, 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Expenses, Petty Cash, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Export Forms, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Financial Statements, 1986-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3-5)
    - Gallery Closing, 1994-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
      Scope and Contents note
      Includes 1 floppy disk [JT Gallery, QBPRO B/U] (Transfer not possible)
    - Legal Documents, 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Statement of Non-Discrimination, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Exhibition Files, 1975-1995; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 2 Linear feet Boxes 10-12
  Exhibition files document exhibitions held at the Jamison Thomas Gallery, as well as art fairs, expositions, and festivals in which the gallery participated. Records are comprised of research and correspondence files for various exhibitions and include consignment and loan agreements, shipping notifications, purchase and sales receipts, clippings, photographs, and exhibition applications and forms.
  Most of the files are arranged in chronological order, except for general photographs, maps, and schedules.
  - Exhibition Installation Photographs, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition Maps, 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Photographs, 1975-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition Schedules, 1982-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition Schedules, 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition Schedules, circa 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - "Mexican Folk Retablos" (1981), 1976-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "Traditional American Quilts" (1982), 1982-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Hmong Pa Ndao, circa 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "Ritual Masks and Figures of West Africa" (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - "Contemporary Folk Artists of the Pacific Northwest" (1984), 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20-21)
  - Metropolitan Arts Commission Percent for Art Project, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "Pioneers in Paradise" Folk Art Exhibition, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - "Tribal Art of New Guinea" (1984), 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - "Hot Summer, Black Magic" (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Humboldt Cultural Center, "West Coast Folk Artists" (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - "Twentieth Century American Folk Art: Five Personal Visions" (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Art in Public Places, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Chicago International Art Exposition, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - New Talent Show (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Seattle Art Expo, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Southern Folk Art (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - ART/L.A. (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Masks, Inquiries, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Airport Conference Center Show, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - ART/L.A. (1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Artquake Festival (1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Chicago International New Art Forms Exposition (1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - ART/L.A. (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Artquake Festival (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - August Group Show (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - USArt Expo, San Francisco (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - ART/L.A. (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Artquake Festival (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - "Contemporary West Coast Sculpture" (1990), 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - ART/London (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - ART/L.A. (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Chicago International Art Exposition (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - ART/L.A. (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 23-24)
  - ArtFair Seattle (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Chicago International Art Exposition (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - "Sign of the Cross" (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - "Spirit of the West" (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Bumbershoot Arts Festival, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Chicago International Art Exposition, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "Language Made Visible" (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - New York Outsider Art Fair (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Southern Folk Pottery (1993), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
  - ART/L.A. (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - ArtFair Seattle (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Artquake Festival (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Outsider Art Fair (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - New York Outsider Art Fair (1994), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "15th Anniversary Group Show/ Final Show" (1995), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "The Dress as Form and Symbol" (1995), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - "Flower Show" (1995), 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Publicity Files, 1980-1996; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 1.5 Linear feet Boxes 12-14
  Publicity files consist of correspondence between the gallery and various magazines, periodicals, and newsletters. Most of the correspondence are requests for advertising, with mock-ups and layouts of ads for exhibitions and general gallery advertisements. Also found here are press releases and articles about the gallery and its shows.
  Arranged alphabetically by publication title.
  - Ads/Promos, Portland Area Guides, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Advertising, Past Records, 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Advertising Contracts, 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Advertising Rates, 1985-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Artcoast, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Artforum, 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - ARTnews, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Artweek, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Art in America, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - ArtsOregon, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - The Fine Art Index, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - First Thursday, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - First Thursday, Blueline, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Fred Stern, Publishers Representative, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Gallery Networking Information, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Graphics, Ann Marra, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Graphics, Bill Dean, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - House and Garden Article, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Interview, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Jamison Thomas Gallery Estate, Artist Talks, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 34)
    Includes 4 sound cassettes.
  - Mississippi Mud, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - National Council on Education for the Ceramic Arts, Gallery Promotion, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - The Oregonian, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Oregon Magazine, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Photographs for Press Release, Gallery Artists, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Portland Downtowner, 1987-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1982-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 7-16)
  - Preview, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 18-19)
  - Printed Materials, Gallery Articles, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials, Gallery Clippings, 1983-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 21-23)
  - Printed Materials, Mailers, 1980-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 24-29)
  - Printed Materials, William Jamison Clippings, 1985-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 30-32)
  - Promotion Layouts, circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Raw Vision, circa 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Reflex Magazine, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - TASA, The Art Services Agency, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Visions Art Quarterly, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - The Weekly: Seattle's Newsmagazine, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Zyzzyva, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Artists' Files, 1940-1996; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 14 Linear feet Boxes 14-28
  The artists' files represent the bulk of the records and were created by the gallery to keep track of artists whose work they exhibited and/or were of interest. Among those represented in the series are Robert Gilkerson, Gregory Grenon, Dan May, Jon Serl, Rick Bartow, Mark Bulwinkle, Jay Backstrand, Stuart Buehler, Mark Calderon, Baba Wague Diakite, and Gus Van Sant. Materials included in the artists' files are correspondence, photographs of artwork, sales records, payments to artists, articles, talks, price lists, photographic prints, slides, exhibition files, and printed materials. Due to the nature of the material as reference files, some of the artists' files predate the years that Jamison Thomas Gallery was open.
  Arranged alphabetically by artist's surname. Where multiple files exist for one artist, the additional notation was assigned by the gallery.
  - Abbey, Patrick, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Abbey, Patrick-Photos, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Abbey, Patrick-Slides, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Abouljaami, John, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Allan, Mary, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Allan, Mary-Slides, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Arensmeyer, Paul, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Arnold, Steven, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Backstrand, Jay, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15-18)
  - Bale, Jeff, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Banks, Ken, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Banyas, Martha, 1984-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
  - Barnes, Mary, 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 23-25)
  - Bartow, Rick, 1985-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 26-33)
  - Bartow, Rick, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1-6)
  - Bartow, Rick-Payments to Artists, 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bartow, Rick-Publicity, 1985-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Bartow, Rick-Price List, Statement, Resume, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bartow, Rick-Resumes/Statements, 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Bartow, Rick-Slides, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Bettendorf, Sherry, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Block, Andrew, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Blosser, Nick, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 14-16)
  - Bourdette, Christine, 1988-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17-19)
  - Bourdette, Christine-Payments to Artist, 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Bourdette, Christine-Photo File, 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Brown, Peter, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Bruch, Cris, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Buck, Chad, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 24-25)
  - Buck, Chad, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Buehler, Stuart, 1985-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2-11)
  - Buehler, Stuart-Award Nomination File, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Buehler, Stuart-Big Apple Circus, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Buehler, Stuart-Inventory, Folk Art Gallery, 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Buehler, Stuart-Letters, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Buehler, Stuart, 1985-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 16-18)
  - Buehler, Stuart-Payments to Artist, 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Buehler, Stuart-Price and Inventory, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Buehler, Stuart-Travel, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 21-22)
  - Bulwinkle, Mark, 1985-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 23-25)
  - Bulwinkle, Mark, 1988-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
  - Bulwinkle, Mark-Historic, 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Bulwinkle, Mark-Old Working File, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
  - Bulwinkle, Mark-Payments to Artist, 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bulwinkle, Mark-Photos(Medium), 1985-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Bulwinkle, Mark-Photos (Large), 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Bulwinkle, Mark-Photos (Small), circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Butler, John, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Butler, Ken, 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
  - Calderon, Mark, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15-19)
  - Calderon, Mark-Photos, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 20-21)
  - Caprario, Kathleen, 1981-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 22-24)
  - Childers, Dennis, 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Childers, Russell, circa 1980-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
  - Childers, Russell, 1978-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Childers, Russell-Payments to Artist, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Colclough, Jim, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Couch Amigos (Cindi Di Prima and Storm Tharp), 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Cramer, Tom, 1985-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
  - Cunningham, Dennis, 1988-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 11-13)
  - DeLave, Mary, 1985-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Diakite, Baba Wague, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15-20)
  - Diebenkorn, Richard-Slides, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Donahue, Marcia, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Doughton, Steve-Fetishes, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Dureau, George, 1977-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Elliott, Dick and Jane, 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Erceg, Ruza, 1981-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 2-5)
  - Erceg, Ruza-Duplicates (Slides), 1974-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Erceg, Ruza-Early Work (Slides), 1975-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Erceg, Ruza-Masters (Slides), 1975-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Estes, Richard, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Estrada, Philip, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Estrin, Amy, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Firestone, Alan, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Fischel, Eric, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Flechemuller, Jacque, 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 14-15)
  - Flechemuller, Jacque-Slides, 1989-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Fritzius, Harry, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 17-19)
  - Gallery History, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Gilkerson, Robert, 1983-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 21-23)
  - Gilkerson, Robert, 1984-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
  - Gilkerson, Robert-Correspondence, 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Gilkerson, Robert-PR, 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Gilkerson, Robert-Slides, 1983-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8-10)
  - Glasscock, Pamela, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Glasscock, Pamela-Slides, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Gordon, Ted, 1983-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Gray, Stephen-PR, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Gragg, Randy, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Grenon, Gregory, 1983-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 16-20)